Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0536., 1871; 000882
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0540., 1871; 000886
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0576., 1871; 000922
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0634., 1871; 000980
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0650., 1871; 000996
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0833., 1871; 001179
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0903., 1871; 001249
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0908., 1871; 001254
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0954., 1871; 001300
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0980., 1871; 001326
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0981., 1871; 001327
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0991., 1871; 001337
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1013., 1871; 001359
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1032., 1871; 001378
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1062., 1871; 001408
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1063., 1871; 001409
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1190., 1871; 001536
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1360., 1871; 001706
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1441., 1871; 001787
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1622., 1871; 001968
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1679., 1871; 002025
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1680., 1871; 002026
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1718., 1871; 002064
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1724., 1871; 002070
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0373., 1872; 000719
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0569., 1872; 000915
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0588., 1872; 000934
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0683., 1872; 001029
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0716., 1872; 001062
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0717., 1872; 001063
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0815., 1872; 001161
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0982., 1872; 001328
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1041., 1872; 001387
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1057., 1872; 001403
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1109., 1872; 001455
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1174., 1872; 001520
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1175., 1872; 001521
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1204., 1872; 001550
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1225., 1872; 001571
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1387., 1872; 001733
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1456., 1872; 001802
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1472., 1872; 001818
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1518., 1872; 001864
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1579., 1872; 001925
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1604., 1872; 001950
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1616., 1872; 001962
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1620., 1872; 001966
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1629., 1872; 001975
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1677., 1872; 002023
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1698., 1872; 002044
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1736., 1872; 002082
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0485., 1873; 000831
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0524., 1873; 000870
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0552., 1873; 000898
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0580., 1873; 000926
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0678., 1873; 001024
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0692., 1873; 001038
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0755., 1873; 001101
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0767., 1873; 001113
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0797., 1873; 001143
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0851., 1873; 001197
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0955., 1873; 001301
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0994., 1873; 001340
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1017., 1873; 001363
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1052., 1873; 001398
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1116; M & A finding aid lists the name as "G. A. Maartz". The correct name is "George Augustus Maack". MAT., 1873; 001462
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1129., 1873; 001475
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1132., 1873; 001478
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1186., 1873; 001532
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1219., 1873; 001565
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1222., 1873; 001568
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1422., 1873; 001768
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1462., 1873; 001808
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1663., 1873; 002009
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1676., 1873; 002022
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0390., 1874; 000736
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0404., 1874; 000750
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0419., 1874; 000765
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0441., 1874; 000787
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0442., 1874; 000788
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0490., 1874; 000836
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0493., 1874; 000839
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0746., 1874; 001092
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0769., 1874; 001115
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0783., 1874; 001129
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0841., 1874; 001187
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0880., 1874; 001226
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0961., 1874; 001307
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0970., 1874; 001316
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1029., 1874; 001375
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1038., 1874; 001384
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1119., 1874; 001465
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1158., 1874; 001504
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1177., 1874; 001523
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1198., 1874; 001544
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1221., 1874; 001567
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1254., 1874; 001600
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1262., 1874; 001608
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1380., 1874; 001726
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1398., 1874; 001744
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1401., 1874; 001747
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1419., 1874; 001765
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1466., 1874; 001812
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1484., 1874; 001830
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1486., 1874; 001832
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1503., 1874; 001849
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1539., 1874; 001885
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1564., 1874; 001910
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1600., 1874; 001946
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1640., 1874; 001986
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1691., 1874; 002037
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1729., 1874; 002075
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0450., 1875; 000796
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0505., 1875; 000851
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0516., 1875; 000862
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0535., 1875; 000881
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0648., 1875; 000994
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0680., 1875; 001026
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0697., 1875; 001043
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0740., 1875; 001086
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0838., 1875; 001184
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0844., 1875; 001190
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0861., 1875; 001207
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0886., 1875; 001232
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0907., 1875; 001253
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0959., 1875; 001305
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1024., 1875; 001370
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1025., 1875; 001371
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1039., 1875; 001385
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1155., 1875; 001501
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1246., 1875; 001592
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1334., 1875; 001680
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1355., 1875; 001701
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1356., 1875; 001702
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1363., 1875; 001709
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1375., 1875; 001721
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1492., 1875; 001838
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1553., 1875; 001899
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1557., 1875; 001903
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1578., 1875; 001924
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1713., 1875; 002059
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0375., 1876; 000721
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0503., 1876; 000849
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0508., 1876; 000854
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0590., 1876; 000936
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0605., 1876; 000951
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0627., 1876; 000973
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0741., 1876; 001087
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0745., 1876; 001091
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0750., 1876; 001096
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0763., 1876; 001109
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0817., 1876; 001163
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0857., 1876; 001203
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0862., 1876; 001208
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0898., 1876; 001244
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0918., 1876; 001264
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0952., 1876; 001298
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1007., 1876; 001353
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1042., 1876; 001388
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1048., 1876; 001394
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1091., 1876; 001437
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1208., 1876; 001554
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1220., 1876; 001566
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1286., 1876; 001632
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1319., 1876; 001665
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1372., 1876; 001718
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1374., 1876; 001720
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1383., 1876; 001729
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1423., 1876; 001769
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1444., 1876; 001790
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1468., 1876; 001814
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1471., 1876; 001817
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1507., 1876; 001853
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1545., 1876; 001891
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1567., 1876; 001913
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1599., 1876; 001945